ILGWU Local 23-25 Records 5780/059
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- GIDCC enrollment lists, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Discrimination, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Citizenship/Legalization Study Materials, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Citizenship Class; Local 23-25
- Political Education Classes, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program, 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program, 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- "Facts for You", 1988 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Local 23-25; materials for new members
- "Some Facts for Stewards" (Box 12, Folder 10)
  Publication of NE, Western, PA and Ohio Departments
- May Ying Chen notebook, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  includes names
- Consortium Adult Literacy Program (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Consortium for Worker Literacy (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Materials, Ideas, and Topics for English as a Second Language and Bilingual Education, 1986-1993 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Local 23-25; Chinatown
- ESL Teaching Materials, including on Triangle Fire, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Labor-ESL Class, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  Teaching material; 1 of 2
- Labor-ESL class, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  Teaching material; 2 of 2
- Rainbows (magazine), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  Student magazine from ILGWU members and families in Chinatown
- ILGWU/Chinatown Level I Curriculum, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Daycare Survey Results, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Opening Announcement, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Daycare Center Press Coverage, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Daycare Center Press Releases and Photos, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Daycare Center Press Coverage, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Daycare Center Opening Ceremony Press Coverage, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Daycare center Press Coverage, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Daycare Center Press Coverage, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Biltrite Daycare Survey, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- "A Childcare Study of the new York City Garment Industry", 1991 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  GIDC;1 of 2
- "A Childcare Study of the New York City Garment Industry", 1991 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  GIDC; 2 of 2
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown Anniversary Dinner Programs, 1984-1988 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Chung Park Dinner, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  Fundraiser
- GIDC Day Care Survey, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown Fashion Show, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Garment Industry Day care Center of Chinatown Application Material, 1983-1991 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Chung Park child Care Center, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Chung Park child Care Center, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Chung Park Project, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- ILGWU Campaign for Justice, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- NYC Garment Industry Info, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation Training, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- GIDC News, 1990-1995 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Asian Labor Committee; Asian Labor Festival, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Asian Labor Committee; Festival Flyer and Art, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Asian Labor Committee; Festival Commitments, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- ALC; Asian Labor Festival Press Work, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- ALC; Asian Labor Festival Finance Records, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- ALC; Asian Labor Festival Program, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Asian Labor Committee, 1989-1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- New York City Asian Labor Committee, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Asian Labor Committee Notes and Agendas, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Asian Labor Committee Members, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Asian Labor Committee, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Asian Labor Festival Booths, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Asian Labor Festival, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Asian Labor Festival Permit Applications, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Asian Labor Festival, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Asian Labor Festival Contributions, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Asian Labor Festival, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Asian Labor Issues, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- APALA Convention Delegates, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- APALA Convention Delegates, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance Convention, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  Chinese Materials
- Asian Pacific American Labor Support Group, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  AFL-CIO
- Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance notes, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Community Council of Greater New York "Public Attitudes and Resentments: Asian New Yorkers", 1986 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  Conferences
- Conference on Immigrations Reform and Control Act of 1986 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO Department of Community Services "Organized Labor-Working Together to Meet Human Needs", 1987 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  November 18
- The National Immigration and Citizenship Forum "From Community Tension to Inter-Ethnic Cooperation: Next Steps for Asian-Pacific Americans", 1987 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Columbia Conference, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  "Managing Workforce Diversity in America: Imperatives for Meeting Tomorrow's Challenge"
- Asian Labor Conference, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  Cornell U.
- Human Services Providers Advisory Committee; Fall Networking Conference, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Immigrant Students: Their Needs and Legal Rights; Training Conference, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Asian Labor Committee; Receipts and Blank Checks (Box 13, Folder 33)
- City of NY Management Speaker Forums, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- National Association of Latino Elected and Appointed Officials; NALEO conference on Citizenship, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Women, Work and Family: Taking Charge, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  March 17
- " We came to work, not to die" Conference for People of Color and Low Wage Workers, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Asian Americans for Affirmative Action Conference, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Building Bridges: Deaf Workers in the Labor Movement, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  April 3
- Joint Conference of Japan-USA Textile and Apparel Workers' Union, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Background materials submitted by ILGWU
- ILGWU New York-New Jersey Staff Conference on Labor-Management and Industry Development Programs, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Conferences, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Conferences, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Conferences, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Low Wage Workers Conferences List, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Advisory Commission for Students with Limited Proficiency in English, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Asian American Studies, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Asian Americans for David Dinkins, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Asian American Heritage Festival, 1982-1990 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- AIM (Associate ILGWU Member) Organizing Kit, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Bangladesh Independent Garment Workers Union, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- SoHo Manufacturing Company, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Boycott
- Brooklyn Chinese-American Association, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Cabin Creek Films Proposal for "More Than Half the Sky", 1990 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Caesar and Napoli Attorneys at Law, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Calendar with notes, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Campaign for Justice (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Campaign for Justice Strike at Domsey Corporation, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  Brooklyn, NY
- Campaign for Justice, Strike at Rainfair, Inc, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  Racine, WI
- Center for Immigrants Rights Paralegal Course in Immigration Law, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Center for Labor-Management Policy Studies, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  CUNY
- Vincent Chin Rally/Candlelight Vigil, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- China Flood, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Chinatown Labor Fair, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Chinatown Labor Fair, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Chinatown Labor Fair, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Chinatown Labor Fair, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Chinatown Labor Fair, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Chinatown Labor Fair, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- CT (Chinatown?) Office Notes, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Chinese Morning Clippings, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  Translated
- Chinese New Year Celebration, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Chinese Pre-Retirement Seminar, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Chinese Pre-Retirement Seminar, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Chinese Pre-Retirement Seminar, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Chinese Pre-Retirement Seminar, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Chinese Pre-Retirement Seminar Planning Committee, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Chinese Pre-Retirement Seminar, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- "City Originals: Women Making It Work", 1994 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  film
- "The Civil Rights Challenge for Asian Pacific Americans in the Next Century", 1994 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- "Class in New York City", 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Film by Christine Noschese
- Coalition of Supporters of Kaity Tong, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  WABC-TV Eyewitness News
- "We Want Kaity", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Coalition of Supporters of Kaity tong
- Commemoration of 1st Anniversary of Tiananmen Square Massacre, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Report and Recommendations
- Committee to Re-Elect Po Ling Ng, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Community Contracts, 1989-1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Community Contracts, 1989-1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Community Council of Greater New York, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Contract Negotiation, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Contract, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Contract, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Contract, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Coordinator's Guide: Basic Union Counselor Training, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Cornell Courses, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Cornell University; Labor Advisory Council, College of Human Ecology Council, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Department of Associate Membership (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Delegate to NYS President Primary/AA for Jesse Jackson, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- "Diversity" Curriculum, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Michael Dukakis, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- East Coast Asian Student Union and Students, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- IlGWU Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  Eligibility requirements and benefits information
- Education Committee Final Report, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Educational Task Force Service Sub-Committee on Staff Training; Final Report to GEB, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Electoral Phone Scripts, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Employer Sanctions, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Executive Board Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Fire Drill, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Free Trade, 1988-1993 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- From the Ashes: A Toy Factory Fire in Thailand"; International Confederation on Free Trade Unions, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Garment History Project, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Garment Workers Justice Center, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- ILGWU Health and Safety Department; NY/NY Staff Seminar, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  43507
- ILGWU Health and Safety Manual (Box 15, Folder 34)
- "The Hidden Cost of Fashion"; Textile, Clothing, and Footwear Union of Australia, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Homework, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Homework Petitions, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Against lifting the ban on homework
- Homework, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  includes ILGWU et. Al reports
- Huang, Yong Xin, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Immigration forms and instructions, 1982-1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Immigration Miscellany, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Trainings, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- International Women's Day, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Kamhi Strike Leaflets, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Labor-Management Relations Panel, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  March 16
- Susan Cowell testimony at Subcommittee on Women; NYC Council, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act Compliance Assistance Kit, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Local 23-25, 1982-1987 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  Leadership Institute; Contracts; etc.
- Leadership Training Program, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  includes photo
- Leslie Fay Strike, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  Press Releases; Clippings
- Leslie Fay Strike, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  Leaflets; On the Line: Bulletin for Leslie Fay Strikers
- ILGWU Local 105 Health and Welfare Fund Meeting Minutes, 1971-1982 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Local 105 Health and Welfare Fund Meeting Minutes, 1971-1982 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Local 132-98-102: Shop Steward Manual, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Jay Mazurs Articles, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Management Engineering Department ILGWU Training Seminar, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Miscellany, 1985-1992 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Misc. Printed Materials, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Miscellany (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Labor Publications and Research, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Misc. Research on Women, Unions, etc., 1995 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Miss Saigon issue, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  produced by Cameron MacKintosh
- Mission Statement (ACTWU/ILGWU), 1995 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  English, Chinese, Spanish
- Mt family Union and Rio Grande Workers Alliance, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Bert Nakano, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  nominee for ACLU Medal of Liberty
- Nanjing Film, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  by Christopher Choy and Nancy Tong
- Nation; "How the Other Half Lives Now" and Letter to the Editor, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Filing a Job Discrimination Charge: A Do-It-yourself Packet, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  National Immigration Law Center
- NYC Commission on the Status of Women, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  1 of 3
- NYC Commission on the Status of Women, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  2 of 3
- NYC Commission on the Status of Women, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  3 of 3
- NYC Commission on the Status of Women, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- NCY Commission on the Status of Women; Public Hearing on Domestic Violence, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- NYC Commission on the Status of Women, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- NYC Elections, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- NYC Issues, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  includes testimony of May Ying Chen and Alice Ip
- Immigrant Petitions, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  The New York Immigration Collation
- New Yorker articles, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  on Chinatown; includes letter to My Chen; June
- May Chen Notebook, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- May Chen Notebook (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Organizing, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- PACE (Professional and Clerical Employees), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Pico/Korean Workers Issue, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Piece Rate Guides, 1978-1983 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Piece Rate Guides, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Pocono Manor, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  Shop representatives seminar
- A Policy Guide on Enforcing the Union Agreement, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  published by Northeast Department ILGWU
- Policy, Union's Response to Immigration and Refugees, 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- "Price Settlement Guide: Sportswear and Blouses", 1975 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- P.S. 20 Proposal, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Queens College, Labor Advisory Board, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Radio/Television, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Radio Scripts, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Rally for Fair Wages for Garment Workers, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- "Reaching for Their Rights: Asian Workers in NYC" by May Ying Chen, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Report on Federal and State Civil Rights Law, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  Civil Rights Dept. ACTWU
- "Report on Summer '89 ILGWU Chinatown Voter Registration" by Pamela Mac, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Rodino Immigration Reform Bill (H.R. 3810), 1986 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Rodino Immigration Reform Bill (H.R. 3810), 1986 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- School Board Election, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Shop Reps, 1984-1990 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  Local 23-25; 1 of 2
- Shop Reps, 1984-1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  Local 23-25; 2 of 2
- Shop Representative Classes, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Shop Rep Classes, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Shop Representatives' Notebook, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Special Manhattan Bridge Project, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Strike Leadership Training Session of ILGWU Activists, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Studies for New York Garment Industry, 1983-1991 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Talking UnionOne-On-One; AFL-CIO Training Program for One-On-One Coordinators, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- CCTN Television Spot, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Textile, Apparel, and Footwear Act of 1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Tribute to MLK, Jr., 1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Unemployment Action center, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Union Health Center Annual Report, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Union Health Center Tuberculosis Guide, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- UHC-Member Assistance Program; Staff Meeting with George Bailey, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  October 7
- UHC-MAP; Spring Conference Planning Committee, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- UHC-Map; Spring Conference Planning Committee, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- UHC-Map; Spring Conference Planning Committee, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- UHC-MAP; Spring Conference Planning Committee, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- UHC-MAP; Spring Conference, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- United nations; Allegations Regrading Infringements of Trade Union Rights, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- United States Commission on Civil Rights, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- "Union Voice", 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  Local 23-25 Radio Program
- "Union Voice", 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- "Union Voice", 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- "Union Voice", 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Women's Action Alliance; Leadership in Action Awards, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Women's Health Report, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Workers Defense League (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Your Union and Your Health; Tamiment Meeting, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Amendments, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Congressional Budgeting Office, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Congressional Lobbying Kit for April Recess Meetings, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Prepared by Campaign for Health Security
- Democratic Bills, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  Mitchell, Gephardt
- ERISA, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1924
- Finance Committee; Moynihan, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Health Alliance, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Managed Competition, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Marks; Health Care Reform Mark Summary, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- McDermott-Wellstone, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- New York City issues, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Premium/part-Time Issues, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Retirees, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Right Wing Attacks, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Single Payer Background, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Single Payer Press, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Single Sponsor Healthcare, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- National Single-Payer Campaign, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- National Single-Payer Campaign, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- State Single Payer Option, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Taxing Benefits, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Television Advertisements, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Women and Healthcare; CLUW, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Workers' Compensation; Health Security Act, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Speeches, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Speeches, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Speeches, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Speeches, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Speeches, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Speeches, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Speeches, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Speeches, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Speeches, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Press Releases, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Press Releases, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Press Releases, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Press Releases, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Press Releases, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Press Releases, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Convention, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Committee on Organization Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  Convention
- Convention Resolutions (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Convention Resolutions, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Convention Transcript, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Fashion-Forward: Newsletter of the Council for American Fashion, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center Annual dinner, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center Annual Dinner, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Garment Industry Day Care Dinner, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- GIDC News, 1990-1994 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Guide for Operating Prices (Box 20, Folder 28)
- "Our First Fifty Years" Knitgoods Workers Union Local 155, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- History of Local 10 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- ILGWU History, 1975-1991 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Homework; Sweatshops, 1986-1991 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- ILGWU/ACTWU Merger, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- ILGWU/ACTWU Merger Press Clippings, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Legislative Department, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- New Members Information Kit, 1990-1999 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Union Health Center, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Photos Artwork, 1938-1979 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- From the Chinatown Press, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  October 5 to April 19
- From the Chinatown Press, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  April 21 to August 2
- From the Chinatown, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  August 3 to January 4
- From Chinatown Press, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  January 5 to June 11
- From Chinatown Press, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  June 13 to November 6
- From Chinatown Press, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  November 11 to April 28
- From Chinatown Press, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  April 30 to November 19
- From Chinatown Press, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  January 2 to May 25
- From Chinatown Press, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  May 26 to March 22
- From Chinatown Press, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  March 24 to September 4
- From Chinatown Press, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  September 13 to March 15
- From Chinatown Press, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  March 14 to July 3
- From Chinatown Press, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  July 5 to December 26
- From Chinatown Press, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  December 31 to September 8
- From Chinatown Press, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  September 9 to January 28
- From Chinatown Press, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  January 28 to May 29
- From Chinatown Press, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  June 2 to November 15
- From Chinatown Press, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  November 19 to May 6
- From Chinatown Press, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  May 12 to January 10
- From Chinatown Press, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  January 7 to May 25
- From Chinatown Press, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  May 26 to December 9
- From Chinatown Press, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  December 31 to May 15
- From Chinatown Press, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  May 19 to October 7
- From Chinatown Press, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  October 9 to December 23
- From Chinatown Press, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  December 25 to April 4
- From Chinatown Press, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  April 10 to June 7
- From Chinatown Press, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  June 7 to December 11
- From Chinatown Press, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  January 17 to July 17
- From Chinatown Press, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  July 31 to April 21
- From Chinatown Press, 1998-2001 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  February 19 to April 25